

Marcos San Millan Fadrique

Regalia Suites Kuala Lumpur No.2, Jalan Anjung Putra Off, Jalan Sultan Ismail, 50480 Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia **E-mail:** MarconiusMarx@hotmail.com **Website:** marcosmarconius.wordpress.com

Phone: +0034 644884123

SUMMARY

A versatile and creative writer who fuses a solid academic background in journalism with an eclectic work experience in marketing, copy writing, web content management, media analysis and educational and cultural diffusion. A wide grounding in languages, traveling and living overseas, a sharp cultural curiosity, as well as an active presence on various social media, depict a versatile, open minded, flexible and multitask professional, ready to excel in the fields of communications, writing and media.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Limkokwing University of Creative Technology

17th July 2014 — 14th February 2015

Marketing Executive (International)

Elaborating market researches, strategies and campaigns; recruiting and enrolling students; establishing partnerships with agencies and educational institutions all around the world; conducting counseling and student services; organizing and supporting in educational fairs and open doors venues; and supporting the company in terms of internal and administrative tasks, team reports and databases, translation services and others.

Media Tenor International AG

June 2013 — October 2013

Media Analyst

Marking-up and coding selected media and publications from EEUU, UK, Italy, Spain and Latin America; participating in regular training sessions; and supporting the company in terms of operation, various researches, training, translation services, graphics and others.

Euromed Carrefour Sic

September 23th 2009 — July 23th 2010

Intern Voluntary Service

Developing the Password Project, an European Voluntary Service Project consisting on a series of informative an educational sessions performed for pupils from medium schools (12-13 years old) and students from high schools (17-18 years old) of Sicily, introducing them to various cultural, social and institutional contents about the European Union. Organizing other informational and educative events; cooperating with other organizations; and supporting the company in web contents and organizational tasks.

University of Valladolid

January 2007 — July 2007

Intern

Developing a Grant of Collaboration in Formative Projects within the Press Office: managing the University's online agenda; writing website announcements and contents; supporting photograph databases; interviewing personalities from inside the

Marcos San Millan Fadrique

1

Campus; and performing copy writing preparing press notes and press dossiers.

EDUCATION

Master of Advanced Journalism- September 2010 — October 2012 Reporting

Ramon Lull's University of Barcelona

Bachelor of Journalism

October 2003 — July 2008

University of Valladolid

QUALIFICATIONS

- First Certificate in English (FCE), University of Cambridge ESOL.
- CILS-3 degree in Italian knowledge, University for foreigners of Siena.
- Arab dialectal basic course at the Language's Centre of the University of Valladolid (2006-2007).
- Identity, Multicultural and Education Course at the Buendía's Centre of Valladolid (7 and 8 March 2005).

LANGUAGES

- Spanish as mother tongue.
- Advanced knowledge of English.
- Proficiency knowledge of Italian.
- Intermediate knowledge of Portuguese.
- Beginner level of French, and basic notions of Vietnamese and Arab.

VARIOUS SKILLS

- Word, Excel, Power Point, Adobe, Picture Manager, In Design, Photoshop, Light room, Final Cut.
- Social networks, digital media, online agenda manager.
- Windows and Mac.
- Twitter: Marcos San Millán @MarcosSMF
- Facebook: Marcos San Millan Fadrique
- Pinterest: Marcos San Millan
- Wordpress Blog: marcosmarconius.wordpress.com
- Linkedin: es.linkedin.com/in/marcossanmillan85
- Open Water Diver.
- Driving license B type.

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Experience as conference host
- Experience as babysitter.
- Participant in Spanish and European work camps: 2009 and 2010 summer camps.
- Participant in Youth Exchange European Programme: Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, June 2009.
- Participant in European Voluntary Service Programme: Palermo, Italy, September 2009 - July 2010.
- Participant in AIESEC Global Community Development Internships: Step Out Project, Hanoi, Vietnam, 20th February 30th March 2013.
- Participant in AIESEC Global Internships: Limkokwing University of Creative Technology, Cyberjaya, Malaysia, 17th July 2004 - 14th February 2015.
- Wide experience in living in foreign countries: Torino, Italy (September 2007 July 2008), Palermo, Italy (September 2009 July 2010), Hanoi, Vietnam (February October 2013), Kuala Lumpur and Cyberjaya, Malaysia (July 2014 July 2015).

INTERESTS

- Literature, cinema, comic, graphic novel, rock and folk music.
- Usual practice of swimming, trekking, gym, running and diving.
- Interested on different cultures and customs, traveling and learning new languages.